Robert F. Queeney

Minneapolis, Minneapolis Cell: (347) 481-7431

e-mail: robert.queeney@gmail.com

portfolio: https://github.com/Robert-Queeney

PROFILE

Developer/Account Executive/Tech Savvy/Program Developer

Accomplished Senior Account Executive with over a decade of sales and service excellence making transition to Software and Web Development. Recognized and rewarded by past organizations for being a quick study, driving revenue growth, increasing brand loyalty and injecting a personable and team spirit to the organization. Humble and consultative style collaborates effectively with teams to ensure the best delivery outcomes.

Education

Full Stack Development Certification

University of Minnesota - 02/18 - 07/18

Recent Projects

React API Demo - Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JSX, JSON, React. A React-based web application that makes an API call using fetch and dynamically renders elements.

Gaming Dashboard - Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React. A compact stateful application for a gaming startup company that allows players to allocate "points" to various gaming components.

Boring Political App - Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Firebase, Bootstrap. A multi-page website that makes a series of api calls based on geolocation and user input to render relevant information.

Donation App - HTML, CSS, React, Node.js, Express.js, Mongoose, MongoDB, Material Design. A group project. This is a fully functional website built as a template for nonprofits to use. It incorporates responsive layouts, easily customizable react components, and an integrated payment system for taking donations.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Developer

January 2018 - Present

 Worked on various web and application assignments, including updating websites' javascript functionality and creating applications using React.js.

Kelly Services

November 2017 - January 2018

Account Executive

- Partnered with HR and hiring managers to provide talent in open positions within new customers
- Prospected new and dormant accounts through traditional cold calling techniques
- Planned and conducted sales calls with prospective and dormant customers

West Corporation, New York, NY (Remote position) Digital Media / Event Services Sales

May 2016 - June 2017

Accountable for selling enterprise-wide presentation, streaming, and communication solutions to well-branded and respected organizations including Avon, CBS, Honeywell, Gartner, CA Technologies, NBC, CHUBB, and IPG.

- Presented complex, enterprise-wide solutions to a number of departments, including Marketing, Communications, Procurement, Technology and Network Teams and the C-Suite
- Partnered with Clients' IT and Networking teams to present, sell, and implement ECDN and peer-to-peer software defined streaming solutions
- Consistently exceed activity and monthly revenue goals of \$160k and above

Brandpoint

January 2016 - April 2016

Account Executive

Develop completely new book of business into marketing agencies and international associations. Selling a mix of established products ranging from PR distribution solutions to newly developed SaaS based content management software.

ON24, Inc., Manhattan, NY Senior Account Executive

April 2014 - May 2015

- Consistently hit monthly sales targets of \$60,000 by generating new business with companies within the Fortune 1,000 category. Notable wins include: Forbes Media, Henry Schein Inc., TUV, Avon, The Environmental Defense Fund, and Citi.
- Achieved ranking of # 8 out of 50 at the start of 2015

Citrix Systems – Online Service Division , Jersey City, NJ Corporate Onboarding Manager

July 2012 - April 2014

- Actively contributed to the launch of Corporate Onboarding Team that provided high value to the customers
 in transitioning over to the Citrix platform, thereby enhancing their initial experience, helping to retain their
 business, and grow revenue within existing enterprise clients
- Achieved and held shared quota of over \$5M
- Contributed to the development of Citrix OSD's onboarding program, creating a streamlined, centralized and efficient process
- Translated field sales experience into the training process that drove relevancy, knowledge transfer, change management and adoption

Citrix Systems – Online Service Division, Tempe, AZ Account Executive

February 2010 - July 2012

- Created new business relationships for the company through a consultative and targeted sales process
- Implemented strategic planning to expand Citrix OSD footprint within assigned accounts, with a focus on cultivating strong relationships with primary contacts
- 2 Time Achiever of Representative of the Month
- Achieved President's Club status for exceeding expectations

PROFESSIONAL / PROGRAMMING SKILLS

React, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, Node.js, MongoDB, MySQL, jQuery, Salesforce, Microsoft Office Suite, Internal CRM systems, Enterprise Software

COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT

Habitat for Humanity, ASPCA